<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FoxCorp</title>
    <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FoxCorp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:02:01 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://foxmaccloud.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackfield - Hack The Box</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/hackthebox/blackfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:02:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/hackthebox/blackfield/</guid>
      <description>Summary Blackfield is hard Windows box. Account enumeration is easy because the box has anonymous access to profiles$ share. That allowed to build custom list for users and find an account with DONT_REQ_PREAUTH flag set: support. The account has policy allowed to change password for non-admin accounts and thus gain access to memory dumps made by audit2020 account. Extracted NTLM hash for svc_backup allowed login to the box and abuse sebackup/serestore to root the domain and then extract administrator ntlm hash from NTDS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pwnable - Start</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/posts/2020/06/pwnable-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 18:49:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/posts/2020/06/pwnable-start/</guid>
      <description>I started doing pwnable a few months back. I think the site is very cool and very good for learning basic binary exploiting skills. I wanted to add some more contents to this site so I made a writeup for the first challenge.
My first writeup can be found Here
There will be more writeups comming in the future, but I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on making a writeup for the Fatty machine from Hack The Box first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start - Pwnable.tw</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/pwnabletw/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 16:48:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/pwnabletw/start/</guid>
      <description>This challenge is quite simple, it has no protection against the hacker. Just use buffer overflow to change the return address and you can leak stack address. You can then send your shellcode to get the flag.
 Finding the buffer size I used a tool Overflow Exploit Pattern Generator generating a 50 character long string. Running the executable trough tools such as GDB Enhanced Features (GEF) and checking the contents of the EIP registry, we can see the string 6Aa7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fatty - Hack The Box</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/hackthebox/fatty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 01:03:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/hackthebox/fatty/</guid>
      <description>Box enumeration  Ports opened:  nmap -sC -sV -A -T5 -Pn -oN nmap 10.10.10.174 Nmap 7.80 scan initiated Sat Feb 8 20:06:13 2020 as: nmap -sC -sV -A -T5 -Pn -oN nmap 10.10.10.174 Warning: 10.10.10.174 giving up on port because retransmission cap hit (2). Nmap scan report for 10.10.10.174 Host is up (0.050s latency). Not shown: 990 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 21/tcp open ftp vsftpd 2.0.8 or later | ftp-anon: Anonymous FTP login allowed (FTP code 230) | -rw-r--r-- 1 ftp ftp 15426727 Oct 30 12:10 fatty-client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic - Hack The Box</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/hackthebox/magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/writeups/hackthebox/magic/</guid>
      <description>Enumeration  Only two ports are open:  nmap -A -T5 -Pn -oN initial-nmap-scan 10.10.10.185 # Nmap 7.80 scan initiated Sat Apr 18 22:30:30 2020 as: nmap -A -T5 -Pn -oN initial-nmap-scan 10.10.10.185 Warning: 10.10.10.185 giving up on port because retransmission cap hit (2). Nmap scan report for 10.10.10.185 Host is up (0.048s latency). Not shown: 971 closed ports, 27 filtered ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/posts/2020/05/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:34:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/posts/2020/05/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hi, and welcome to my new domain!
I made this website using the Hugo framework instead of writing up own html &amp;amp; css. I will use this website to post all my content, ideas and future projects. I will also add writeups for challenges at a later date, so stay tuned!
Check out whoami for more information about who I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‎‎‎‎&gt; $ whoami</title>
      <link>http://foxmaccloud.com/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 05:29:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foxmaccloud.com/whoami/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Fox Maccloud! I started getting into infosec when I was about 17 years old. It all started messing much earlier with video games and computers as a kid and wondered how shit works&amp;hellip;
I sadly was not able to really get into hacking at this age since searching &amp;ldquo;How to become a hacker&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t exactly yield any decent results.
Skipping a few years, last year of highschool I started to learn how to do programming mainly python and set up services such as game servers and other services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>